ELSA FARAH FAUZIA

BACHELOR OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (HONS.)

SUMMARY

Highly motivated fresh graduated candidate. My nationality is Indonesia and I was born at Palembang, 21 June 1998. Previous job exposure in oil, manufacturing, logistics and supply chain company. 3 years of organizational experiences and is passionate in business and technology. I would be delighted to have an opportunity and I certain that my experiences will prove to be beneficial to the company.

CONTACT INFO

+601120928315

in /in/elsafarahfauzia

elsafarahf@gmail.com elsafarahf.github.io



EDUCATION

Universiti Utara Malaysia, 2017 - Present

BSc. Information Technology (Hons.) Minor Computer Network | CGPA: 3.62

SMA Plus Negeri 17 Palembang, 2013 - 2016

Majoring in Sciences

PROJECTS

2020, Smart Reporting Mobile Application Final Year Project Using Flutter and Dart Language

2018, Smart Irrigation System (SIS) Prototyping IoT Project for UniMaker Regional Competition 2018

SKILLS

Public Speaking IT Project Management

Advance Advance

Software Analysis and Test

Advance

UI/UX Design

Intermediate

HTML, PHP, MySQL, JavaScript

Intermediate

Routing and Switching (CCNA)

Intermediate

Java Programming

Basic

LANGUAGES

English (ELPT Band 7.5)

Advance Native

Indonesia Malaysia

Advance

REFERENCES

IMRAN USMAN

HR PERTAMINA RU III Imran.u@pertamina.com

DR. IDYAWATI BINTI HUSSEIN

Supervisor of Final Year Project idyawati@uum.edu.my

WORKING EXPERIENCES

Ninja Van, Indonesia | October 2020 - Present

Software Quality Assurance Intern

- Execute all levels of testing in company's business unit and product
- Analyze and create test case scenario using Cucumber and Jira tools
- Detect software defects and inconsistencies by request APIs in Postman

Vechnology Sdn Bhd, Malaysia | May 2020 - June 2020 IT Engineer (Part Time)

- Updating front-end website using react.js
- Connecting database using local Firebase
- Diagnose and fix bug performances

PT PERTAMINA (Persero), Indonesia | Jan 2019 - Feb 2019

Communication and CSR Intern

- Review and analyze proposal sponsorship
- Media monitoring and handling along to create press release and stakeholder mapping

ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCES

2018 - 2019, Information Technology UUM Association (I-TECH) **Deputy Executive Committee of Integration and International Affairs**

- Successfully conducting an industrial visit as Deputy Director to the Flagship E-Government Services and Digital Engineering Services company
- Executive Committee of Innovative Research, Invention and Application Exhibition (I-RIA)

2017 - 2019, ENACTUS UUM

Senior Executive (SE) of Aquanom Project and Multimedia Department

Assist in the development of entrepreneurial project which is a combination of both agriculture and fishery, and creating a poster design for events

2017 - 2020, CAS Representative Association (CRA)

Executive Committee of Integration and International Affairs

- Conducting the international events such as Secretariat of ASEAN Youth University Summit and Treasurer of UUM-ASEAN Leadership Journey Thailand
- As a buddy to assist an exchange international student in re-registration

ACHIEVEMENTS AND AWARDS

Dean List Award 1st, 3rd, 4th, 5th, 6th Semester By School of Computing (SOC) UUM

Excellent Academic Achievement 2nd Semester 2017/2018

By College of Arts and Sciences (CAS) UUM

TOP 20 UNIMAKER REGIONAL 2018 MAKEATHON

By Director, Industry Relation Division Ministry of Education Malaysia

CERTIFICATES

Aug 2020, The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing

By Google Digital Garage | ID Credential: R9Q RVF 5UF

Aug 2020, Project Management Certified

By StudySection | ID Credential: 203654

Aug 2020, Introduction to Cybersecurity

By CISCO | Issued using Acclaim